[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Scientists hope that in the future wind power will be able to ____ 50% of the electricity we need.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is essential to consider her difficulties at school in the ____ of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Since Ramadan emphasizes ____ aspects and since everyone eats dinner at the same time, Muslims often invite one another to share in the Ramadan evening.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Her efforts have continued to ____ in the last few months. I think she may be having problems at home.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has become unpopular recently and is ____ to lose the coming election.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A ____ and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too vague or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Very ____ water does not conduct electricity well compared with contaminated water because it contains no inorganic ions.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Looking up all the key words in an important ____ should be considered a background check for all literary analysis.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The regime, which is bound to ____ under the deadweight of its own internal contradictions, is going to ____ on our heads.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Numerous policy and ____ implications were derived from the study findings.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Roman walls of Oberursel still ____ and surround almost all of the old town center.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The fact that he can only speak a little English is sure to ____ his already severe learning problems.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug ____ underlie many serious health problems.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's potential and her ____ place in life.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Good writing is concise. A sentence should ____ no unnecessary words, a paragraph no unnecessary sentences.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your final course grade will ____ on your grades in the 3 trimester exams.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers and parents can learn and ____ ideas for helping to work for more successful outcomes in the transition from school to adult life.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to invest a lot of ____ over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These programs must ____ factors that may be affecting profits.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are one or two ____ spelling problems but in general this is an excellent piece of writing.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course is intended to ____ a lot of class discussion.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Can you please use a ____ ruler to draw straight lines, not the side of your book.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to try and ____ your thoughts a little more clearly. This does not make much sense to me.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more ____ policy positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They are never forgotten, those brief moments of splendid ____ sandwiched between so many slices of rancid defeat.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ of being himself. Immigration laws have required him to pretend to be somebody else.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to ____ the duties of the typical teaching job.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too ____ a method of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Storage of personal information not ____ to university business must be limited and must not interfere in any way with the storage and maintenance of university data.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most significant ____ factor in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Law School will not permit you to take a ____ pass/fail unless you have received written permission.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Beyond this, if you have a ____ reason for absence or coming in late, such as a documented medical excuse, you should provide that information to the instructor.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I think her problems in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ to develop a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new manager needs time to ____ her own style of leadership.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Whatever I write on the board in class as the next day's assignment will always ____ what is printed in the Class Schedule below.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you want to live a long and healthy life, it is ____ that you eat well and get plenty of exercise.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "\"We hope to ____ the historic value of these buildings and encourage serious parties to step", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His idea is ____ not feasible - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a serious shortage of workers in the ____ of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a ____ speed at all heights.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government faces a ____ decision: Does it anger the USA or does it anger its European allies?", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To ____ the project, a special event will commence at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The German army planned to ____ as far as Moscow, but were then stopped by the severe Russian winter.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Users want to maximize their access to ____ information, without losing sight of the amount of energy it takes them to get that information.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police chief set up a committee whose ____ was to investigate the reasons for the shooting of the wrong man.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a symptom of a greater cultural ____ that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These budgets must be very carefully designed as it is extremely difficult, if not impossible, to ____ the amount of the award once it has been granted.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We need to ____ a test to measure the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best survival ____ for one part of the organization is usually not the best ____ for another.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "On the rare occasion when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than pure hatred, his observations ____ to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some scientists claim that we cannot ____ global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has continued ____ me with her hard work and positive attitude.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this class, we will examine the ____ about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you cannot obtain such a statement, you must verify that you have contacted your employer and that the employer was unable to ____ you with the refund.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most language teachers use ____ aids in the classroom, such as pictures or objects.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The supervisor will judge whether the paper is satisfactory, and ____ she or he should make sure the student has enough preparation.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The developing world does not ____ many industrial wastes; thus it has had little opportunity to develop proper disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many of the students were unable to ____ the relevance of the mathematics they had learned and so could not make use of it.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The study also found that both genders get a similar benefit from the therapy, which reduced mortality ____ in women by an estimated 43%.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It should be ____ that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the prime cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The findings directly ____ the assertion that some verbal areas of the brain are larger in women than in men.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ was too much for some, and owners were forced to sell their homes at a reduced price.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These programs must ____ factors that may be affecting profits.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is planning to make a ____ tomorrow morning on its discussions the doctors' union.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please ____ the Timetable for class times and locations.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Wurtz said that these products are not just ____ unnecessary, they are even potentially dangerous.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even though the right hemisphere could not communicate to observers what stimuli it had been presented with, it did show some ____ comprehension.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As we ____ the end of the school year, it's time you started to work a little harder!", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These orders do much to ____ the significant need for better organization in terms of record-keeping.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly ____ hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government tried hard to ____ its decision, but most people believe it was a serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a profound effect on the ____ of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not ____ to enforce it.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Law School will not permit you to take a ____ pass/fail unless you have received written permission.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He has a heavy accent but this does not ____ with understanding what he means.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ the linguists, for not insisting that anyone who claims to be an educated person needs elementary competence in describing and analyzing the sound, form and meaning of human language.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences gradually improve ____ over time.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The internet is a ____ resource for today's students.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is a very ____ example for demonstration purposes. However, the effect is similar for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The management has made a ____ promise but now it needs to be put in writing.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its reluctance to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lorelei's fine efforts in starting and maintaining the list have done much to ____ group communication and interaction.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The university has no obligation to refund the ____ after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can ____ your risk of getting a cold in the winter if you avoid others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was a time when priests were experiencing financial crisis and the Church was unable to ____ many of their expenses.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He said that any art teacher who did not ____ students to ten thousand years of art was \"criminal.\"", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ my teacher for not preparing us properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can ____ this book until the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is a ____ that Japanese girls are quiet. You should hear them on the bus on a school trip!", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum ____ for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a ____ excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you ____ the data further, you will see that there are many observations that are larger than 600.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is a well-known fact that smoking is a ____ of lung cancer.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If faculty suspect that a ____ health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government reduced its ____ to the Arts Council after it was found that much of the money had been wasted.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The twins ____ most of the weekend to their fishing hobby.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's potential and her ____ place in life.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The high price of oil will ____ much of the company's profits this year.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is English expression which claims: All roads lead to Rome. This means that there is more than one ____ to fame and success in life.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Although the mountain was not steep, the raging river could not descend with sufficient rapidity to ____ its overflowing its banks.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The majority of American voters have turned ____ the war in Iraq but not ____ the American troops and not ____ patriotism.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Too much stress can trigger problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new committee just adds another ____ to an already complex decision -making process.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Carla Santos, a professor of leisure studies, says our perception of another culture is ____ shaped by accounts of travel writers, who tend to perpetuate cultural stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They may have been unwilling to ____ information to an unknown group with unknown intentions.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a valid excuse, you can ____ the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not always easy to ____ student progress.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last ____ of the flooded village was evacuated by a helicopter.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What is ____ in your essay is any reference to the source of your ideas.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government shows little ____ into the reasons why so many young people become addicted to drugs and alcohol.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Martin Luther King was killed ____ for insisting that America could not continue with people isolated on lonely islands of poverty.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a ____ far greater than its economic substance.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teaching profession is under siege from an increasing number of social, ____ and political factors, leading to large, unmanageable classrooms.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people look back on their years at university as the happiest ____ in their lives.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Internet businesses will only be successful if they use the ____ of clear, easy, cheap, safe shopping.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the departure times are not ____ for you, there is a list of recommended car and taxi services available as well.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students will need to ____ a spokesperson to speak for their group and come to an agreement about their decision.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Since we can't ____ it directly, we need to infer it from the things we can ____.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions emerge in that moment, in the ____ of their description.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Picasso's ____ to draw found expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many universities make their materials ____ to students online.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Strong families ____ the ability to manage both daily stressors and difficult life crises creatively and effectively.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My ____ to work every day takes me past my old school.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a rational decision but ____ one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ workforce is opposed to the managers' plans to relocate the factory.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government failed to understand why the people were so unhappy with its policies, and ____ was voted out at the next election.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our ____ surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is not a business. Its goal is not to make a large profit, but to ____ enough money to provide the best possible education.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Then you will need to ____ the selection criteria you want to use.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to do a better job when you ____ your work. There are far too many unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Omitting the transportation costs would ____ the company's financial position.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is extremely important to ____ the installation with all parties involved.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the words 'uninterested ' and 'disinterested'.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The catheter then deploys a small balloon at the ____ of the blood clot.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The practice test materials will become available just ____ to the class.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small ____ was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Numerous policy and ____ implications were derived from the study findings.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of applications will continue until all positions are filled.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since the early 1990s, the number of smokers has continued to ____ but at the more gradual rate of 5.2% annually.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We should seriously pursue the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally ____ option.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to induce ____ changes in society.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In 1986, 23 percent of parents said obedience was the most important ____ they expected from their children.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will ____ more rapidly if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The outcome of our ____ is that most students are against school uniform.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We should not ____ the costs, minimize the benefits of what we have already achieved, or downplay the risk of failure to persevere.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police need to ____ more evidence before they can make any arrests.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of the student as the school's primary customer provides an important guiding principle for many of today's school reforms.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "form"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Roman walls of Oberursel still ____ and surround almost all of the old town center.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Luckily, ____ to total coincidence, the men's and women's basketball teams started most of their games on the road.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most scientists ____ that the life expectancy of people in developed countries will continue to rise.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this article I will discuss the possible use of ____ speech recognition (ASR) for training students to improve their accents in a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My regular mathematics teacher is sick so we have had a ____ for the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government said that it had no ____ to give the reasons for its decision.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must unite and ____ institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The district cannot ____ the accuracy of the information or the appropriateness of any material that a student finds.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company won the ____ to supply the government with 30,000 special computers for primary schools.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Older people should have a ____ check-up at the doctors at least once a year.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you look carefully, you will ____ that the ice is starting to melt.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university has no obligation to refund the ____ after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes ____ and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to diverse cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The rat lungworm, is the ____ cause of eosinophilic meningitis worldwide.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the ____ to the general public in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is will ____ to undergo problems in its attempt to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the new science building is not finished yet, but from the outside it looks great!", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These ____ and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable expense to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Niehuss does much to illuminate the enormous ____ of consumer culture on West German women's lives.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Everyone knows the dangers of smoking, yet hundred of young people start the ____ each year..", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What is the exact change in ____ of the water when it freezes as ice?", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most students are ____ about the suggestion to replace the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much credit by conducting a ____ after all the superior officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The paper was unable to attract sufficient ____ and ceased publication after a few months.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the ____ eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant function of state and ____ governments.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Educational websites have the ____ suffix: .edu. For example, the URL of this website is: esl.fis.edu.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most economists believe that oil is the most important ____ in today's world.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or ____ and then hoping to transform it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the ____ of a problem and that symptoms may often overlap in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Congress is resolved to ____ online gambling in America.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Even though the right hemisphere could not communicate to observers what stimuli it had been presented with, it did show some ____ comprehension.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government was fully ____ of the magnitude of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I gave him clear ____ how to do the experiment, but he obviously wasn't listening.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The report was designed to measure computer and Internet use ____ people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The results from this experimental course illustrate very clearly that flow visualization can be performed successfully by a wide ____ of people.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Of course she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the ____ stage of learning English.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too vague or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Student Activities Committee presented a project designed to raise awareness of the ongoing ____ in the Sudan.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The online instructor must ____ the best practices of traditional teaching without the benefit of face-to-face interaction.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it ____ and therefore decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I ____ to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to attend the lectures.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ your good mood if it's hot and loud in the classroom, you have a headache, and the work is very boring.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company director decided to ____ his son as the new head of marketing.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At the same time, we believe that the victory over ____ and hatred is achieved one person at a time.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teacher said that he could not ____ to grade all the papers by the next lesson.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Therefore, if a calf has not received an ____ amount of quality colostrum, the calf may not be able to resist disease.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors have found a connection between cannabis use and mental illness. This is ____ a danger for people who have started taking drugs at an early age.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Having access to the laptop does seem to have substantially increased the ____ feeling of having adequate resources to do the job.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Illegal immigration is not the prime reason so many ____ young blacks are on the streets and why some turn to gangs, guns and drug dealing.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You do not need to consider the whole of human psychology, but you should make a ____ between good excuses and bad excuses.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She will need an ____ performance to have any chance of winning the game. Her opponent is much better.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ is to find the right mixture of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The basic ____ is, and always has been, one of parenting.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Strauss said his health started to ____ and he was placed on the transplant recipient waiting list.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug abuse ____ many serious health problems.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will ____ your chances of success if you are absent from school so often.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She was in ____ with her parents at home and this was having a negative effect on her schoolwork.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Due to the recent increase in student numbers, the school can now ____ to build a new science laboratory.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A major problem for most western societies is how to ____ immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Copying from the internet has grown on a large ____ in recent years.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You are making very ____ progress in learning English! You only started learning a year ago, and you can already speak quite fluently.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people who use a wheelchair or mobility devices do not ____ them as confining. They are viewed as liberating; a means of getting around.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Political Bureau will work to ensure the smooth ____ of the reform of the administrative system.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our teachers ____ the school's philosophy that only excellence is good enough.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will culminate in a ____ of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To ____ these opportunities, information systems will need to sense and act as well as compute.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is ____ true in the environmental sciences where many of the systems are dynamic and extremely complex.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking point within the sentence, for ____ before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bernstein thinks the survey is very important to students and that schools should not ____ it.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Business Index provides a one-stop resource of information on: small business management, foreign ____ opportunities, job hunting strategies.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ordinary people who are caught up in ____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The lessons that ____ lunch today are cancelled for a special assembly.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ of sentimentality in Weil's notion of the beauty and order of the world.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My regular mathematics teacher is sick so we have had a ____ for the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This was a ____ attempt at addressing the issue, and not a very scholarly or intellectual attempt.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The University may ____ the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written notice to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the ____ use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If a student is caught with drugs in the building, the school will ____ him or her.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He also was able to assist in identifying outstanding science curriculum materials for the teachers in the ____ to review.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Before buying a new house you need to ____ a tax advisor.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ____ people who are caught up in extra____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was little ____ to the government's proposals to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Those who had seen the march in Weimar at the 1926 party rally knew that National Socialism's march to ____ could not be halted.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ how much people should or should not drink.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She has made fairly good ____ this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a deliberate attempt to ____ the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The study of Growth and Development can help us to know a person more thoroughly and ____ be better doctors.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors ____ that people eat 5 fruits or vegetables every day.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ response of the Hu Jintao government has won widespread praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase income tax after ____ demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to ____ the world's languages into one comprehensive genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is an obvious ____ to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a ____ at our school to have a pizza party for the new students.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All students must ____ at the beginning of the school year that they understand and will follow the plagiarism policy.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you have the amnio test late in pregnancy and are carrying a baby with Downs Syndrome, it will be too late to ____ the pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The number of students in the school will continue to ____ in the next few years as Frankfurt increases in popularity.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The tree responds this way because the tree needs to ____ food again before it starves.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ocean is a ____ of both freedom and escape.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With noise levels of this magnitude, hearing ____ is a distinct problem unless some sort of hearing protection is used.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The findings directly ____ the assertion that some verbal areas of the brain are larger in women than in men.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new government has promised not to repeat the mistakes of the ____ one.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In decimal notation we represent a negative number by writing a minus in front of a ____ number.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was a ____ in the cafeteria at lunch today. The oil for cooking French fries ignited and set fire to the wooden ceiling.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since it was founded in 1999, the partnership program has been a ____ element in the dramatic increase in applications to the College.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The court also held that because of the ____ between the classification society and the shipyard, the owners operated the ship under the French flag.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't comply with police orders to ____ from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Applying the engineering feedback concept, we can search and reach the optimum ____ with a very small number of tests.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His problems are largely ____ to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In fact, most nations do not admit immigrants for ____ settlement.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite ____s in a deliberate attempt to conceal the ____ of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people used to believe that if cancer did not ____ within five years, a person was safe.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Open Office Writer is ____ of saving documents in many different formats.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When a ____ court heard the case, it found the policy did not violate students' free-speech rights.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ to sit next to John any more. He never lets me work.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a hostile or abusive work ____ which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project ____ date.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Miller, long a ____ of Switzerland, broke with the school of traditional psychoanalysis over the issue.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This was not characteristic of Serbia alone; the population felt ____ frustration in other parts of Yugoslavia and in Eastern Europe.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the consistent use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be ____ the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Government ministers should not ____ on matters outside of their own domain; they often do not know enough about such topics.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Desdemona is passive for much of the play and when she dies at the end, she takes the ____ for her death.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we do not start to ____ less oil, there is likely to be none left by the end of the century.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To separate white light into its ____ colors with a prism and use an identical prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Increased ____ caused consumers to spend more and firms to invest more.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They ____ decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The high price of oil will ____ much of the company's profits this year.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ must not risk damage to any personal or public property.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teacher was asked to ____ after it was discovered that he had lied about his absence from school.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If children of seven years and older will be included in the study, an ____ agreement is necessary.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most have concluded that no logic of discovery exists and, moreover, that a ____ model of discovery is impossible.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a ____ speed at all heights.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A regular driving ____ does not entitle the ____ holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its ____ updating, people will be able to discover new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The dentist needed to ____ my back tooth. It had become badly infected.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These programs must ____ factors that may be affecting profits.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could hardly fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ of accidents and a mounting public demand resulted in the government licensing of pilots and aircraft.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will ____ all house owners to exchange their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These budgets must be very carefully designed as it is extremely difficult, if not impossible, to ____ the amount of the award once it has been granted.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This paper documents ____ findings from a nationwide survey that investigates substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so ____ to allowing ordinary parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "From my perspective as a teacher and parent, I would say that her difficulties in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ was determined by querying the number of research proposals received by RSPP and the direct costs associated with reviewing each proposal.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government must not ____ in taking harsh actions against communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The European Union attempts to align commercial and financial practices in its ____ countries.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school has a ____ of approximately one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is a particular ____ to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Photographs ____ if they are left out in bright sunlight.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their instinct whether it is safe to ____ a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to trust your ____ as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was not willing to ____ from previous legal commitments.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to discuss global warming. Many people say that the whole ____ was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mobile phones ____ parents to keep in contact with their children when they are out with their friends.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "No program has developed an approach that is ____ successful in working with the types of problems that we try to solve.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "C. S. Lewis tackled this issue head-on and offered some good advice that informs how we ____ our projects.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A significant ____ to setting up a new business is the enormous amount of documentation that has to be completed.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Children like to ____ cars or buildings from plastic bricks.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Eat less, ____ more: the formula for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We must ____ the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the former grade will remain on the ____ with an appropriate notation.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In my opinion the government's ____ for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government ____ was cleared of protesters by riot police and police horses.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She found, however, that there is no documented process for achieving a ____ response to adversity.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his ____ to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ over whether North Korea will collapse and whether the United States should promote its collapse has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The drive to excel must be ____ in the culture of a university.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The links between ____ price declines and food prices are not easy to discern.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In our previous class on binary counting, we found a way to ____ numbers using just two digits, 0 and 1.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not ____ with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee ____ announced his intention to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This unnecessary war will ____ the government plans to reduce tax.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to ____ or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to ____ prejudice.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government refused to ____ from its plan to ban smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Scientists have not been able to ____ that the fossil is in fact that of a dinosaur.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, ____ a huge debt to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Requiring students to leave the school building at lunchtime is not a very popular ____ from the new principal.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are responsible for gathering all ____ necessary to support an appeal.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Tourists who visit a foreign city often employ a ____ to show them the most interesting things to see.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This past summer, after a vacation to Japan, I realized that what I had been eating in America was not ____ Japanese food.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "According to him migrants and refugees do not ____ enough in Dutch society.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a hostile or abusive work ____ which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The temperatures did not ____ as much this month as they did last month.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The supervisor perceived Pullard as an incompetent employee, but did not ____ that he might be a security problem.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning technique to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A sound card is an essential ____ of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She wanted to ____ and to reorganize the departmental program but was not able to convince the school administration.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Less than 10% of students who need basic skills education and don't get it ____ in college.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of native-English speakers and non-native-English speakers at the school is about 40% : 60%.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The strategy used for the actual campaign was ____ different.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These were very industrialized nations but their economies did not ____ the high levels of consumer spending we see in the First World.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the ____ question, namely how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's good that the school employs employ new, young teachers every year. They can ____ discussions about teaching methods.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The volume of business between Europe and Asia has ____ increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, ____ ten per trimester is liable to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In this paper we describe simple identification and signature schemes which ____ any user to prove his identity and the authenticity of his messages.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He is ____ considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to assume key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The problem for France was that the population did not ____ of responsible citizens which were necessary for the desired liberal system.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Lack of financial ____ is a significant constraint on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most basic technique to ____ is observational drawing skills.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is a ____ topic, unless you already have some knowledge of superconductivity.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You should be able to ____ the answer if you think carefully enough.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to ____ global problems, since they have also failed to ____ their own domestic problems.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is noted that the university regulations stipulate that a course can be offered only if a ____ number of students is enrolled.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He came to the conclusion that Mexico's constitutions did not last because they simply did not ____ to Mexico's customs and traditions.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Look at the ____ of your book. Did your dog try to eat it?", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The high price of oil will ____ much of the company's profits this year.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base regarding the ____ of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The circumstances that led to the ____ crash are being investigated by the police.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It should be obvious that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the ____ cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Parents often ____ their children's choice of clothes or music..", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They must ____ their information so that it is easy for the observer to understand the historical significance of their event.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government neither intends to comment on the event nor even to ____ that it actually happened.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Human rights activist John Prendergast, who will present the lecture \"Stopping Genocide\", is ____ the notable speakers coming to campus.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Chromatography is a separation ____ that is used in virtually all branches of science and technology.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The tale ends with Gilgamesh, at the end of his ____ standing before the gates of Uruk.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She should be able to ____ to take care of the children on \ufffd\ufffd200.00 per month.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They failed to publicly ____ the message that climate change will having a direct negative impact on global security.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Rules do not usually ____ creativity or passion; rather they demand conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When you finish unit 1, please do the questions and then ____ to unit 3. You don't need to do unit 2.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ teacher request to students who are not listening in class is: Pay attention.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bone marrow may ____ cells lost in vision diseases.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice ____ program is barely alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and function of cities and ways planners ____ urban problems.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When attempting to ____ a food service for an on-campus event, please be sure to ask the following questions.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The University will ____ the cost of the premiums for graduate students during the coming academic year.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The chairman decided to ____ the meeting when people started shouting at each other.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Can you please give me the final ____ of your writing? This looks like your first draft before you corrected the spelling and grammar.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an image war, trying to ____ the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, ____ underlying issues, and suggest alternative resolutions.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a ____ in my family for everyone to get together for Sunday lunch.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We used this information to ____ a continuous measure of the ratio of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on ____ drugs but they do not know so much how drugs interact with each other.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to ____ talking unless absolutely necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has only a ____ knowledge of English grammar - not enough to be an ESL teacher.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many soldiers come home from war with no ____ problems, but often they have psychological problems that never really disappear.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students needed to devote considerable time to recognizing the three ____ tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lispeth took to Christianity readily, and did not ____ it when she reached womanhood.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This situation is certain to improve over the next few years, given the ____ of research now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The administrative ____ will inform the student supervisor when a student has failed to provide required documents and other information.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ____ people who are caught up in extra____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There will be no ____ or written personal attacks on any individual or group of individuals based on age, ancestry, color, disability or handicap.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Do not commit the ____ error of believing you can pass the course without doing the coursework.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Generic skills cannot be considered as ____ of subject matter. Moreover, a good part of teaching involves thinking, problem- solving, and decision making.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must ____ with the death penalty regularly.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should follow the ____ that the doctor has given you.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over 100 students marched to the Hoover Institution to ____ a possible U.S. war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum ____ for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school's facilities have been improved ____ with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a standard of living ____ for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He has only ____ control of basic verb grammar. He quite often chooses the wrong tense or forgets the -s ending.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I cannot think of any ____ writers who are better than her.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this ____ of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Iron is a major ____ of hemoglobin that carries oxygen to all parts of the body.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course is predominantly concerned with the social relations of ____ that developed along with the major revolutionary currents of the eighteenth century.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A simple and often effective means to reduce blood pressure is to reduce the ____ of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "FLO plays the key role as an ____ for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions ____ the need for communication or being able to freely display your emotions?", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most educational institutions have a required ____ for citations and references.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to ____ how icebergs in a remote corner of Antarctica can disrupt an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The greatest ____ that we face is to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ the plan after a meeting with the parents.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is a ____ that Japanese girls are quiet. You should hear them on the bus on a school trip!", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Groups should advise the instructor if a member is unexpectedly ____ and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows prior to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government must not ____ in taking harsh actions against communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to impose an ____ crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He wants to get a job in the engineering ____ when he leaves school.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There will be an ____ of 20 minutes in the middle of the school play.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The results from this experimental course illustrate very clearly that flow visualization can be performed successfully by a wide ____ of people.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She had no ____ to practice architecture in the District.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please ____ me from the trip list. I will not be able to go.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The boss was right to ____ that his workers would return to work once it was clear that they would otherwise lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are responsible for gathering all materials necessary to ____ an appeal.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government will never ____ drug-taking, but it should do more to reduce the number of school-age drug users.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding certain sentences that ____ common sense.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When the models incorporate the effects of pollution, they ____ that rainfall will decrease even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to require food manufacturers to ____ their products as high-, low- or medium fat.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people do not ____ a top engineering education with a liberal arts setting.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You should follow the ____ that the doctor has given you.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Audio software can help students to record their spoken words describing an ____ concept or how to perform a computation.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Access to the data network is both an essential tool for university life and work, and a ____ privilege.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and appropriate classroom behavior) tend to be too ____ for many children.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you are caught drinking and driving, this results in an ____ driving ban of at least 3 months.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "On the ship, every ____ room and corner was turned into dormitory space; cots were set up to accommodate the overflow.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at ____ for delegating that function to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This means that you will be able to ____ money from your bank account to your StanfordCardPlan using this new online service.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government met this morning to ____ how to help people who have been hit by the flood crisis.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The best ____ is to change the nutrient solution every week instead of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Results will be published in the ____ issue of the Canadian Journal of Fisheries and Aquatic Sciences.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Patience was not ____ in him, but he developed it under misfortune and opposition.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, owe a huge ____ to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After much debate the school has decided to admit students with ____ disabilities.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "First, you will need to ____ background information about all of the supporting questions.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please bring all your ____ to class. That includes your homework planner and dictionary.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Allies decided that Korea could not ____ itself after so many years of foreign rule.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not the only ____ of teaching we use at the university; instead we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is some ____ that she plagiarized her research essay.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Use positive words and phrases; don't ____ the energy of the interview by focusing on the negative.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Muscles ____ unless they are exercised; just like the brain!", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The main consequence of these wars is the social unrest, and the increasing ____ and social divergence between the groups of the community.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She was making a ____ distinction between causing something and making something happen.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Education is a key ____ in the development of all countries, regardless of their social, political, economic, or cultural characteristics.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Parents often ____ their children's choice of clothes or music..", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ of most big cities around the main train station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an ____ explore topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The communication ____ is a computer, phone line, and modem; the student must have access to the necessary equipment.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He has a ____ chance of getting in to Oxford University if he gets top scores in all his exams.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I gave him clear ____ how to do the experiment, but he obviously wasn't listening.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the ____ of competitive sports, and perhaps elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India ____ cars.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Scientists have found life over a mile below the ____ of the sea, far from the sun.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You must ____ at the top of the page how many words you wrote.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "No wonder your computer doesn't work. You must ____ it to the monitor!", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government would like to reform the health service but the doctors are ____ their proposals.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the classroom doors to make them less easy to break down.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to ____ a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A student should declare a Literature ____ by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant ____ of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote ____ northerners, did not receive a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Niehuss does much to ____ the enormous impact of consumer culture on West German women's lives.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is difficult to achieve success in school if you are ____ so often.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The main ____ of the school is the teaching of science and mathematics.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Class data will be collected to compare perceived overweight and attempt at dieting with ____ weight risk classification.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Preparing yourself for a ____ in oceanography is probably one of the most interesting and rewarding (yet difficult) paths to travel.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to ____ to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her ____ was that the Korean people believe that the U.S. policy is to have a divided Korea and that the U.S. is the reason the two countries are not united.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people advocate government elections every four years ____ of every five as at present.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students will learn to appreciate what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an ____ are associated.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is now clear to me that they shared an ____ inability to view themselves objectively and critically.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "World War II was a turning point because, for the first time, women were allowed to ____ the military.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ me a seat at the back of the school bus.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A ____ of this cement three tenthousandths of an inch thick over one square inch will support a weight of 7000 pounds.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The decision on whether to shut down its nuclear power stations is ____ the most serious issues facing the government.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How do I request that the Libraries ____ a book or other material?", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and ____ of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an entity ____ from its mother?", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at ____ for delegating that function to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Parents who are alcoholics often ____ their children both physically. and emotionally.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is looking for students who would like to do ____ work at the local old people's home.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The significant differences between the traditional and non-traditional student has prompted the question whether institutions need to ____ their teaching methods to fit the needs of the non-traditional student.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The study included a ____ of the main concepts of the authors' model on connecting children with nature and community.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a random sample of a target audience in my county to do a needs assessment or ____ baseline data?", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is of ____ importance that you learn academic vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not engage in any other activities immediately ____ to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the ____ was not steady with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the ____ to improve his rather poor grades.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is planning to make a ____ tomorrow morning on its discussions the doctors' union.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although the patient was in pain, the doctor did not ____ the problem as serious.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You need to trust your ____ as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done ____ the comparison of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Traveling really gives students a better ____ of the world.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The \"Maximize\" position says that we should give ____ to whatever treatment produces the greatest net health benefit.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The service ____ of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing ____.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "form"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is overspending and will soon ____ all the money set aside for books and other materials.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the ____ can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Hopes continue to ____ that a peace treaty can be negotiated.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging task for the employers to determine the factors that ____ job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to ____ on your admissions application that you will have 24 credits completed at the time of attendance.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The instructor is expected to ____ his or her grading policy at the beginning of the course.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some students find it difficult to ____ to a new school in a new country.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The class learns that Alzheimer's disease is a deterioration of cells within the brain that leads to ____ of memory.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Yet there were conflicts there too, and the immigrants did not ____ easily and completely into Israeli culture.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually underlie exceptional performance ____ out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Individual investors: ____ with caution.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The pictures presented aspects of the objects they could not ____ from the equations alone.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of the old people in the home was serious. There was not enough personnel to take care of them.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to ____ to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to ____ to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You must try to ____ a balance between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students gain professional ____ before graduation so that they enter the job market with a distinct advantage.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The management wanted to ____ the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to replace him.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Just ____ someone wakes up after sleeping for thousand years. How might the world look different?", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Performance in the money markets has been ____ in recent months, but prices are expected to fluctuate in the near future.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "often"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We have found that students are more likely to complete a community health project if they ____ a team.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The first effort to produce a revised policy started during the mid-1980s and failed to ____ in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many students ____ their chances of examination success because they only start to work hard a few weeks before.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To separate white light into its ____ colors with a prism and use an identical prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the compulsory stage of education have insufficient ____ educational opportunities.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school has employed an expert to ____ on the best way to use computer technology in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an ____ pattern that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I think Kerry's biggest error, as a politician, is that he failed to ____ himself from Bush in any meaningful way.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To ____ for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a generation efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The management wanted to dismiss the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to ____ him.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we ____ just a little more, we will see that random is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Cole Conservatory evolves from a Music Department with a long ____ of exceptional training for students from all backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at ____ expense to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Latin alphabet did not ____ between the vowel and consonant sounds of i and u.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His new book is sure to ____ a lot of attention.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to ____ the directions of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He questioned the security coordination that enabled the terrorists to ____ all their preparatory work. The authorities had failed to surround the school for three days.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too ____ a method of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I believe police agencies have no right to ____ who can or cannot own guns.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the notion that publishing houses lack sufficient diversity in both high and middle-level ____ members.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The first ____ change in the business model came with Henry Ford's move toward standardization and applying the concepts of a production line to the car.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Here you can recommend areas for investment of resources to ____ the University in its health sciences, education, research, service and outreach missions.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I don't believe that the government's plan to imprison more criminals is the best ____ for the problem of rising crime.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of education and research institutions vested in the common ____ of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to ____ among our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should seriously pursue the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally ____ option.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The essay asks students to complete several tasks, giving the students ____ examples of human rights cases.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no need to enumerate in ____ the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We have not yet been able to find out the ____ reason why he attacked the teacher.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government will monitor the ____ in Iraq very carefully, but has not yet made any changes in its policy.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government had to ____ from its starting position in the face of massive criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to ____ a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is will continue to ____ problems in its attempt to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "After Iraq some people feel strongly that the USA should never again ____ in the affairs of other countries.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The experiment resulted in a ____ that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This page contains a ____ outline to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I can survive on a ____ income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief ____ the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I do not protest about your right to an opinion, but I do protest about your inability to see the ____ when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will need to form project teams of two or three students, and then it will be your responsibility to ____ meetings.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I gave you ____ instructions not to open the box. Why did you disobey me?", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Production of oil and gas will ____ unless new reserves of oil and gas are discovered and developed.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The house was built so carelessly that it began to fall ____ after only a couple of years.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ sector of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing sector.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was a sound idea to ____ the problem before attempting attempt a solution.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Every ____ effort will be made to accommodate properly documented special needs.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the ____ between North and South campuses with two concerts that combine symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should never ____ or blame any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In our society, which is far from uniform in its beliefs and values, reaching consensus on any ____ is significantly difficult.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your ____ is to learn the English words that will help you be successful in your school subjects.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His written work is actually very good, but he has ____ problems with the difficult English spelling system.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can be ____ certain what you read at the government site is accurate and up-to-date.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The principle behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must ____ to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ from Frankfurt to Oberursel is about 12 kilometers.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The results ____ that the best models will almost always incorporate both vertical and horizontal processes.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her mother is a ____ visitor to the school. In fact she comes two or three times a week!", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "often"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While you may not ____ to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous ____ or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The significant differences between the traditional and non-traditional student has prompted the question whether institutions need to ____ their teaching methods to fit the needs of the non-traditional student.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a vital ____ of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to ____ the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The primary ____ of the Management Information Systems Department is to prepare students for exciting and challenging careers in the information technology.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students choosing this option must select a faculty adviser from the departmental faculty who will ____ the student's program.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The only disappointing part of the book is a portion of the third chapter, which is devoted to an interesting but much too ____ discussion of FDR's foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Check the ____ below for specific dates and starting times.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not ____ the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a positive racial identity.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "So when Solomon died (sometime around 920 BC) he left a vacuum of power which his weak son Rehoboam was not ____ of filling.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For most teachers the cash bonus was a nice acknowledgment of work well done, but not an ____ that influenced their behavior.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For most teachers the cash bonus was a nice acknowledgment of work well done, but not an ____ that influenced their behavior.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right mixture of ____ that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is thinking of extending ____ education by two years.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The controversy resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to ____ the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The nurse gave me a ____ for my headache.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While we must ____ all terrorism, and we have many local enemies in various parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has banned smoking in virtually all ____ places.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some beach systems showed significant ____ of sand in the period from 1964.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the ____ operating system will be more secure than ever before.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your final writing must ____ to your research notes, otherwise you risk being accused of plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An exciting and dynamic teacher will receive more ____ results than a teacher who is boring and low key.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Surprisingly little effort, however, has been devoted to the scientific study of how to ____ teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is virtually impossible to predict which infants in the ____ group will not survive without support.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not precise enough to ____ exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Part of the job of an ESL teacher in an international school is to ____ the need to make work comprehensible to non-native speakers.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is to the government's ____ that they refused to participate in the invasion of Iraq.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Obviously the result of many years of reading and reflection, this ____ study contains detailed summaries of dozens of works, both major and minor.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The self-hatred that this ____ inflicted led the children to attempt to wash their skin white with scouring powder.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We are in the middle of the most serious ____ with the governments of these peoples and nations.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The boss took the ____ decision to close the factory for a week.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in ____ but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done ____ the comparison of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students gain professional experience before graduation so that they ____ the job market with a distinct advantage.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is important that the government's proposals do not ____ the development of small businesses.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In Germany most students have the chance to gain ____ experience in an office or factory, before deciding what job they would like to do.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The internet is a ____ resource for today's students.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She had shown no ____ to engage in abusive conduct.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some, but not many, drivers do not ____ to increases in the price of petrol by using their car less frequently.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most people employ an ____ when they want to buy or sell a house.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some, but not many, drivers do not ____ to increases in the price of petrol by using their car less frequently.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Bali has failed to ____ a proposed ten year program to work on sustainable production and consumption.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Roman Catholic Church along with the ____ Protestant denominations in Europe did not oppose the slave trade.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your final course grade will ____ on your grades in the 3 trimester exams.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at ____ for delegating that function to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some beach systems showed significant loss of sand in the ____ from 1964.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you currently do not ____ the skill to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most children take a share of ____ duties such as washing the dishes.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a ____ consideration in the purchase decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to identify him and ____ him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a serious ____ of workers in the profession of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "But the mice did not undergo ____ cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While addiction and drugs are serious problems in society that ____ a humane approach, there is no room for nonsense if we want to achieve success.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because of the increase in the price of oil the company was unable to ____ to its plans to employ new workers.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If they want to ensure more business, they will have to ____ their prices.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She accepted the arduous task of vice president, according to the papers, saying that she could not ____ the will of the people.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Homes were built and sold to families in need at no ____ and no interest.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In recognition of your continuous ____ service to the university, you will receive an award at five-year intervals.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Turning in work completed by other students will only ____ you when it comes to the exams.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and ____ problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We will continue to see new immigrants coming to our city, and we will need to ____ their access into the medical care system.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Biological processes interact strongly with ____ and chemical processes to create the planetary environment.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to accomplish its goal of reducing unemployment ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your answers ____ a lack of care and effort.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the region is sure to ____ an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police ____ that they are doing all they can to find the missing child.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The library is going to extend the space it has made ____ for computers and video screens.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You either are or are not married; it's not a ____ question.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will generate much ____ in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her chances of success in the examinations will continue to ____ unless she starts working harder very soon.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to ____ an offer of the local food.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Harvard is probably the most famous education ____ in the USA.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that random is ____ the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Kennan had no ____ that the Soviets had regional, if not global, ambitions.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To include an ____ on your website, you will need to insert the ____ into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this ____ by 40%.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is research that could ____ help in the treatment of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "At our 10th ____ symposium in late 2005, we posed this set of questions about Space Exploration: Who, What, When, Where, Why?", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Lebanese security officials said the soldiers' tank drove over a mine, but Israel said it could not ____ that.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is heading into difficult ____ with its plans to ban smoking in all public places.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to ____ or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They are currently involved in a ____ against Occidental Petroleum to save their land and their way of life.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The first ____ of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The students decided to unite in their ____ to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a ____ statement describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My research does not ____ contacting people because I intend to use existing or archived material.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Over the past 30 years, the ____ in Africa has continued to deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Don't forget to ____ your research sources at the end of your writing.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "However, no one criterion will be the sole reason for ____ of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My parents ____ a lot of money from their investments in internet companies.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These tips do not relieve you of the ____ to read and follow the Instruction Booklet which is ONLY available on line this year!", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people refuse to ____ Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "His observations were not exact enough to ____ anything significant about nocturnal behaviour.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The suggestion is ____ not reasonable, and the department need not adopt it.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He was not willing to ____ from previous legal commitments.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The final ____ presents the impact of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their effect on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many students doing an important test try to ____ their answers with their hand or a book. They don't want their neighbour seeing what they have written.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The search results are likely to include lots of hits that are not particularly ____ to your topic.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the importance of the internet.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lorelei's fine efforts in starting and maintaining the list have done much to ____ group communication and interaction.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You have a ____ chance of passing your exams if you work really hard for the rest of the term.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are certain to ____ excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has become unpopular recently and is ____ to lose the coming election.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to define any of these abstract terms, and yet I ____ some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is ____ unusual considering the 1997 survey's response of 41%.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company's ____ was to increase sales by 20%. Due to the high cost of oil in the past year, it was not successful.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ for her frequent absences will be a poor grade in the final exam.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Three teachers are going to ____ at the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The information that you ____ in today's lesson will enable you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Use ____ words and phrases; don't drain the energy of the interview by focusing on the negative.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to collaborate ____ our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While we must oppose all terrorism, and we have many ____ enemies in various parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Education is a key ____ in the development of all countries, regardless of their social, political, economic, or cultural characteristics.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The cost will not ____ anyone from participating in the program.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was the result of his labour that Brazil could ____ scientific institutions.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material ____ of Louisiana, it did not diminish the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to ____ from power cycle failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government needs to make a more serious ____ to ensure that all school-leavers have a job.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nature was an intrinsic part of ____ Chinese, Japanese, and Indian literature.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This report summarizes our ____ findings.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The development of ____ communication protocols is a critical issue in today's age of pervasive communication.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Iraq has entered into a critical ____ where there is a great danger of civil war.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Matilda Thurston considered who was the most ____ architect to design a proper campus for 200 students.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The number of students at the school with learning difficulties has begun to ____ in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our results did not ____ us to determine whether SMR or MOEE had reached minimum values.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "From then on, the government tried to ____ the communists of being enemies of the fatherland.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Emma was ____ of these various and strongly held opinions, through professional periodicals.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What the headlines failed to ____ was that democratic parties captured more than 60 percent of the ballots cast.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an ____ occasion to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Digital Libraries constitute a relatively young scientific field, whose life spans ____ the last fifteen years.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The construction of the Interstate Highway System ran into serious financial problems because Congress did not ____ the cost of inflation.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was no pattern to the ____ of the disease.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The result will be an immediate and ____ increase in the number of faculty of color who are tenured at this institution.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Giuliani's leadership during New York City's darkest hours of the September 11th terrorist attacks earned him global ____ and admiration.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most significant ____ factor in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of doctors are hard-working and competent, but there are some who are not.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When attempting to ____ a food service for an on-campus event, please be sure to ask the following questions.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We have not made much ____ toward the fulfillment of Xabier's dream of finding a solution to world poverty.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What if a student alleges that she is entitled to a tuition refund because her instructors failed to ____ the required number of hours of instruction?", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She has no ____ difficulties with English, but she just seems to be learning very slowly.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In issues of accuracy or speed, the ____ must always have priority over the latter.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A nursing or household robot must be ____ in order to reach a variety of working sites within the house.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to ____ how grammar and usage errors can interfere with meaning.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "European governments strongly ____ the kidnapping of a German aid worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When reporting scores, both the student's ____ and the number of students in the class must be stated.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is ____ for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You should ____ your name from the copies of the items you submit.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government claims that it invaded Iraq to bring democracy to that country. Many people, however, claim that this is not a ____ reason to go to war.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We cannot allow a few disaffected children to continually interrupt the ____ of the majority of the class.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There will be a ____ of Chinese art, literature, instruments, calligraphy, and fashion from noon to 4 p.m. on Wednesday, February 27.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her grades will start to ____ unless she cuts back on the number of after-school activities she does.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Internet businesses will only be successful if they use the ____ of clear, easy, cheap, safe shopping.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While mastery of both written and spoken English is considered to be an ____ attribute, students with documented hearing, speech and other disabilities will be reasonably accommodated in accordance with law.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the ____ of the brain.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study programme in the Netherlands, you may be ____ for a grant for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The unexpected shortage of flu vaccine during winter 2004/2005 caused ____ concern.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government met this morning to ____ how to help people who have been hit by the flood crisis.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is going to introduce a law that will ____ smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Not all members of the Bush Administration have been telling the ____ truth about their dealing with Iraq.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to ____ in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The bottom of the Pacific Ocean is the most ____ region on Earth.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Another reason to ____ student e-mail and internet usage is to ensure their safety.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you can't do your homework, you should ask your parents to ____ you.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was an ____ idea to allow the students to write their own test.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to travel at half-price on the trains and buses in Frankfurt, you need a ____ identity card with the school stamp.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This fact demonstrates that immigrants are not ____ to learning the language of their new country.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Describe the study in ____ sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is worth investigation.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no ____ of sentimentality in Weil's notion of the beauty and order of the world.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not always possible to ____ a cause of a conflict from a consequence of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no liberty without law, and no ____ law or legal system when liberty is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to ____ the world's languages into one comprehensive genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The aquarium owner decided sometime in the spring of 1992 to release the animal before any further ____ or an accident with the other dolphins could occur.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You are recommended to record every significant ____ about each of your customers.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Minimum temperatures failed to ____ above freezing until the 26th of the month.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our results did not enable us to determine whether SMR or MOEE had reached ____ values.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most students agree that teachers need ____ them on how much they have learned.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The more powerful computers will continue to ____ all aspects of life.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "So, what's the ____ of all this hindsight and what do we stand to gain from it?", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to ____ higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ to develop a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Using computer modeling, he was able to deduce the ____ between the strength of a stellar wind and the age of a star.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the ____ to induce profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All around the school are small white boxes which can ____ smoke and set off the fire alarm.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We must be ____ in how we interpret the data. It would be easy to draw false conclusions.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You must ____ copies of the primary literature that you are citing to your paper, and you should highlight the pertinent sections.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to impose an ____ crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In the event of an actual ____ a new virtual bulletin board will help the campus take roll.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doubt and mistakes must not be allowed to ____ us because it is from them that we learn.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Before economists implement ____ measures to reduce population growth, further studies should be performed.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the ____ word to convey an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A respect for other cultures is ____ in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In his view, the Empire was less a place where England exerted control than where it lost ____ of its own identity.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to ____ the progress of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have no ____ how difficult this problem is.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has changed its attitude to nuclear ____ now that the cost of oil has been so high for the past few years.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government reduced its ____ to the Arts Council after it was found that much of the money had been wasted.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This opinion is subject to ____ revision before publication in the university journal.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "China is able to manufacture goods cheaply because ____ costs are low.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The contributors assert that teaching is a gendered occupation with low ____ and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In my opinion you are being too ____ if you think you can learn a language in less than a year.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote ____ northerners, did not receive a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Overpraising a person's ____ achievements can be just as discriminatory as undervaluing them.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you ____ a student of plagiarism, you must have strong evidence.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater ____ that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unemployment rates are currently quite stable. There have been no ____ rises or falls in the last two years.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors have not been able to establish the ____ cause of the patient's illness.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first ____ on the agenda is the proposal to increase working hours to 42 per work.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This could substantially change the nature of the Internet we have come to know, to the ____ of both the consumers and the providers of information.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has invited the ____ community to its Open Day.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How can I ____ access to my Web pages?", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Being the best tennis player in grade 7 is not enough to ____ you for the ISST sports competition.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government should ____ making promises that it cannot keep.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A common science ____ for young people is to investigate the growth of plants under different soil, light and water conditions.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ minister has said that he has no plan to resign over the crisis in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As a consequence, it often takes many years of regular water quality data collection to statistically ____ a trend.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My ____ impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to address an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Earth's ____ is divided into four layers, which is typical of rocky planets.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most important criterion for selecting a research ____ is that you are really interested in it!", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She should be able to ____ to take care of the children on \ufffd\ufffd200.00 per month.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has attracted many more German students recently. My ____ is that parents are not happy with the education their children are getting in German public schools.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government failed to meet its ____ of reducing child poverty by 20%.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new ____ will affect all immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ more detail. Your report has lots of general statements but very few precise facts.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a ____ tax sheltered annuity program should contact their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This survey is being used to gather information about the current level of frustration with computers and the ____ to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Hacking's book suffers from a serious defect, ____ he does not understand the nature of hypnosis.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If someone invites you to their party, it's polite to send them a ____ and tell them if you can come or not.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government should pay particular attention to reducing unemployment ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must ____ instruction for students.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}]]